onebazaar.com 2011-05-24

# Privacy Policy - Onebazaar.com

**1) Privacy & Security Policy**

  **Onebazaar.com is concerned & committed to your Privacy **

  We understand the importance of your privacy, hence we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy, where you can know, when you visit our website Onebazaar.com what information we collect, why we collect it, and how & where we use it. This Privacy Policy also addresses our data security practices, the options you have to access and control any personally identifiable information you provide to us, and other matters.

When you use our website, we may request your name, street address, telephone numbers, email ID or other information. We use this information to complete and support your purchases & queries you made on Onebazaar.com website, for internal purposes and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction & queries, the delivery of your order or the support of your use of the Onebazaar.com web site. With your consent, we may also share your information with trusted third party marketing partners. We may also use this to inform you any news, new arrival or happenings in the market. 

  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

  As you browse our web site, we may gather navigational data & IP address that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support your purchases from and use of the Onebazaar.com website and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order and the support of your use of the Onebazaar.com website. 

  We may have to disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, or Onebazaar.com has good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the requirements of law or comply with governmental orders, court orders, or legal process served on Onebazaar.com or (2) to protect and defend the property or rights of Onebazaar.com , the users of its website or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk protection. If Onebazaar.com should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell the information you provide to us on the Onebazaar.com website to a third party or share your personal information with the company we merge with. 

  Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. Onebazaar.com uses cookies to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. They cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information. You must accept cookies to shop at Onebazaar.com . We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. Onebazaar.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and some other browsers, so that only Onebazaar.com can read a customer's personal information. 

  This Site contains links to third party websites, including sites of manufacturers or any other advertisers. Onebazaar.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Your use of these third party websites is entirely at your own risk. 

  By using the Onebazaar.com website, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently. 

  **2) LEGAL DISCLAIMER:  
**   
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We do not claim the information & MRP of the product is correct, we have gathered data from various sources & tried to validate also but we are not responsible for any error in the same. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Mumbai within one month after the claim arose, or be barred.
